

CONTACTS

+48 574 770 827 vit.sydorenko@gmail.com @<u>LinkedIn</u>

@GitHub

<u>@Telegram</u>

Cracow, Poland

HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS
- JavaScript
- Node
- React
- React Native
- Jira

SOFT SKILLS

- Communications
- Multitasking
- Time management
- · Problem-solving
- · Attention to details
- Teamwork

LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Advanced
- English Upper-intermediate
- Polish Upper-intermediate

VITALII SYDORENKO

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

As a recently trained junior front-end developer, I have completed comprehensive IT courses covering HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and Node. While I lack professional experience in the field, I am enthusiastic about applying my newly acquired skills to contribute to a dynamic team and grow as a front-end developer.

PROJECTS

CINEMANIA, GitHub (team project) [HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API]

Role: Developer

About: A captivating website offering a delightful collection of movies, trailers, and information for all the passionate film enthusiasts. Beloved films you can add to the library for the future watching.

<u>Film Searcher</u>, <u>GitHub</u> [HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, API]

Role: Developer

About: Films and images library which fetch data according to your query from API.

ICE CREAM, GitHub (team project) [HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API]

Role: Scrum master, developer

About: Single page website designed for ice cream producer where you can find and order your favorite flavors.

WEBSTUDIO, GitHub [HTML, CSS, JavaScript]

Role: Developer

About: Multi-page website with simple navigation developed for design studio

BARBERSHOP, GitHub [HTML, CSS, JavaScript]

Role: Developer

About: Single page website with few section and submit booking form.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HAVI SERVICE HUB

Procurement and material planning specialist / 10.2021 - PRESENT

- Managing purchase orders and flow of goods at optimal efficiency
- Planning and implementing methods to increase cost savings Managing stock and inbound balancing
- · Liaising with suppliers and distribution center

MOTOROLA SOLUTIONS

Order Management Coordinator / 05.2019 - 09.2021

- Dealing with key partners to achieve supply chain cycle time and quality goals
- Managing and prioritization of critical orders on the first-in, first-out basis
- Working on improvement projects to drive and achieve higher levels in service quality and customer satisfaction

EDUCATION



October 2022 - August 2023

Full-stack developer

[HTML, CSS, JavaScritp, React, Node]

UKRAINIAN STATE UNIVERSITY OF FINANCE AND INTERNATIONAL TRADE

September 2009 - May 2015

Master's degree. Management of Foreign Economic Activity